safehomepage.com 2014-06-01

# Safehomepage.com

### PRIVACY POLICY

Safehomepage.com is committed to preserving the privacy of our users. This Privacy Statement explains which information we collect and how we use it. 

### Collection and Use of Information

In general, we collect and use anonymous information and data regarding your access and use of Safehomepage. When you visit Safehomepage our servers record the information your browser automatically sends whenever visiting or using a Web site, including your web request, the Internet Protocol address and browser configuration of your computer, the date and time of your request, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the referring and exiting Web sites. If you use our search services, we also collect information on the search terms you submit and the links you click upon the results pages. We do not require you to provide us with any information that identifies you personally to visit Safehomepage or use our search services. We generally collect this anonymous information in server log files and use this information for a variety of purposes, including providing you with our search services, the administration and operation of our Web sites, identifying and preventing fraud and misuse of our Web sites, and designing and developing new products and services. 

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Safehomepage.com does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Safehomepage.com may disclose your Personal Information if Safehomepage.com believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Safehomepage.com; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Safehomepage.com (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Safehomepage.com services or members of the public. 

### Security

We are committed to protecting your information. We have adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

### Business Transitions

In the event that Safehomepage.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Safehomepage.com will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Safehomepage.com may have prior to such transfer. 

### Changes to Policy

Safehomepage.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Enforcement

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please direct them to us at the contact information provided below. We have instituted internal policies and procedures for handling such submissions and will respond to you in a timely manner. 

### Contact Information

For any questions or concerns you may have regarding this License Agreement, please complete the below form. 

VIA MAIL: Hefei Feiqiu Info Tech Ltd  
Room 401,Building B3,Animation and Service Outsourcing Industry Base,Hi-tech Development Zone,Hefei. China 

VIA EMAIL: [admin@safehomepage.com](mailto:admin@safehomepage.com)
